apolloduck.co.uk 2011-05-23

# Boats for sale UK, used boats, new boat sales, free photo ads - Apollo Duck

Boat Search  
All Boat Listings  
Auctions  
Private Listings  
Trade Listings  
New Boat Ranges  
Directory

[**Barges**](http://barges.apolloduck.co.uk/) 157  
Boat Builders 21  
Boat Charters 12  
Boat Exchange 15  
Boat Shares 60  
Boat Trailers 97  
Businesses 10  
Canoes & Kayaks 45  
Chandlery 172  
[**Commercial**](http://commercial.apolloduck.co.uk/) 398  
[**Engines**](http://engines.apolloduck.co.uk/) 520  
[**Fishing Boats**](http://fishingboats.apolloduck.co.uk/) 475  
[**House Boats**](http://houseboats.apolloduck.co.uk/) 368  
Hovercraft 2  
[**Inflatable Boats**](http://inflatables.apolloduck.co.uk/) 381  
Marinas & Moorings 101  
Marine Events 2  
Marine Services 38  
[**Motor Boats**](http://motorboats.apolloduck.co.uk/) 1990  
[**Narrow Boats**](http://narrowboats.apolloduck.co.uk/) 1254  
Open Boats 77  
[**Personal Watercraft**](http://pwc.apolloduck.co.uk/) 27  
Rowing 5  
[**Sailing Dinghies**](http://sailingdinghies.apolloduck.co.uk/) 1322  
[**Sailing Yachts**](http://yachts.apolloduck.co.uk/) 1820  
[**Sport Boats**](http://sportboats.apolloduck.co.uk/) 714  
Submarines 1  
Superyachts 17  
Tall Ships 3  
Waterside Properties 23  
Watersports 18  

**Popular Brands:**

**[Bayliner](http://bayliner.apolloduck.co.uk/)**  112  
**[Beneteau](http://beneteau.apolloduck.co.uk/)**  126  
**[Birchwood](http://birchwood.apolloduck.co.uk/)**  44  
**[Broom](http://broom.apolloduck.co.uk/)**  36  
**[Fairline](http://fairline.apolloduck.co.uk/)**  131  
**[Fletcher](http://fletcher.apolloduck.co.uk/)**  27  
**[Freeman](http://freeman.apolloduck.co.uk/)**  44  
**[Hardy](http://hardy.apolloduck.co.uk/)**  39  
**[Jeanneau](http://jeanneau.apolloduck.co.uk/)**  122  
**[Princess](http://princess.apolloduck.co.uk/)**  70  
**[Sea Ray](http://searay.apolloduck.co.uk/)**  60  
**[Sealine](http://sealine.apolloduck.co.uk/)**  113  
**[Seamaster](http://seamaster.apolloduck.co.uk/)**  41  
**[Shetland](http://shetland.apolloduck.co.uk/)**  51  
**[Westerly](http://westerly.apolloduck.co.uk/)**  114

Aberdeen 2  
Aberdeenshire 12  
Anglesey 16  
Angus 3  
Antrim 74  
Argyll and Bute 72  
Armagh 15  
Bedfordshire 28  
[**Berkshire**](http://berkshire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 142  
Borders 3  
Bridgend 3  
Bristol 57  
[**Buckinghamshire**](http://buckinghamshire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 63  
Caerphilly 2  
[**Cambridgeshire**](http://cambridgeshire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 151  
Cardiff 34  
Carmarthenshire 6  
Ceredigion 8  
[**Cheshire**](http://cheshire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 247  
Cleveland 12  
Conwy 10  
[**Cornwall**](http://cornwall.apolloduck.co.uk/) 193  
Cumbria 45  
Denbighshire 9  
Derbyshire 49  
[**Devon**](http://devon.apolloduck.co.uk/) 379  
[**Dorset**](http://dorset.apolloduck.co.uk/) 355  
Down 165  
Dumfries and Galloway 12  
Dundee 3  
Durham 7  
East Ayrshire 2  
East Lothian 4  
East Midlands 10  
[**East Sussex**](http://eastsussex.apolloduck.co.uk/) 62  
[**East Yorkshire**](http://eastyorkshire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 49  
Edinburgh 15  
[**Essex**](http://essex.apolloduck.co.uk/) 432  
Falkirk 2  
Fermanagh 88  
Fife 14  
Flintshire 2  
Glasgow 18  
[**Gloucestershire**](http://gloucestershire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 92  
Guernsey 8  
[**Gwynedd**](http://gwynedd.apolloduck.co.uk/) 218  
[**Hampshire**](http://hampshire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 934  
Hebrides 1  
Herefordshire 8  
[**Hertfordshire**](http://hertfordshire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 83  
Highlands 27  
Humberside 19  
Inverclyde 11  
Isle of Man 9  
[**Isle of Wight**](http://isleofwight.apolloduck.co.uk/) 118  
Jersey 8  
[**Kent**](http://kent.apolloduck.co.uk/) 468  
[**Lancashire**](http://lancashire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 164  
[**Leicestershire**](http://leicestershire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 63  
Lincolnshire 61  
[**London**](http://london.apolloduck.co.uk/) 391  
Londonderry 68  
Manchester 29  
Merseyside 55  
Merthyr Tydfil 2  
Mid Lothian 6  
Monmouthshire 11  
Moray 11  
Newport 2  
[**Norfolk**](http://norfolk.apolloduck.co.uk/) 338  
North Ayrshire 45  
North Humberside 2  
North Lanarkshire 9  
North Yorkshire 45  
[**Northamptonshire**](http://northamptonshire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 126  
Northumberland 20  
[**Nottinghamshire**](http://nottinghamshire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 95  
Orkney 3  
Oxfordshire 76  
Pembrokeshire 37  
Perth and Kinross 12  
Renfrewshire 12  
Rutland 17  
Shetland 5  
Shropshire 31  
Somerset 59  
South Ayrshire 22  
South Humberside 2  
South Lanarkshire 3  
[**South Yorkshire**](http://southyorkshire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 87  
[**Staffordshire**](http://staffordshire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 201  
Stirling 2  
[**Suffolk**](http://suffolk.apolloduck.co.uk/) 239  
[**Surrey**](http://surrey.apolloduck.co.uk/) 168  
Swansea 58  
Tyne & Wear 34  
Tyrone 16  
Vale of Glamorgan 6  
[**Warwickshire**](http://warwickshire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 67  
West Dunbartonshire 5  
West Lothian 1  
[**West Midlands**](http://westmidlands.apolloduck.co.uk/) 69  
[**West Sussex**](http://westsussex.apolloduck.co.uk/) 201  
West Yorkshire 90  
Wiltshire 58  
[**Worcestershire**](http://worcestershire.apolloduck.co.uk/) 78  
Wrexham 8  

About Apollo Duck  
FAQ  
User Agreement  
Copyright Notice  
Privacy Policy

© 1998-2011  

ALL RIGHTS RESERVED

| 

Apollo Duck Privacy Policy

Santa Monica Airlines takes your privacy seriously. Subject to the terms of the Apollo Duck User Agreement, this statement explains our privacy and data-protection practices. 

It is important for Apollo Duck to safeguard its users' privacy while providing a personalised and valuable service. Collecting some personal information is necessary in order to provide a secure service to uniquely identifiable users. 

> What information do we compile?
> 
> In addition to any information given during the advert submission or registration process, information is automatically logged about your browsing behaviour through the site. This log information is only in an aggregate form, and no individual registered user is identified therein. The aggregated data allows us to analyse site traffic and better understand how we can improve the efficiency and value of our services. 
> 
> What do we do with the information we collect?
> 
> The limited personal information you supply on your advert submission form or dealer account registration will not be disclosed outwith Santa Monica Airlines. The email address you provide is used as a simple and memorable username for accessing the service. We may use your address to communicate any changes and improvements to the site and service. Each time you receive a message, you have the option to decline to receive further service communications from us. 
> 
> What information do our cookies collect?
> 
> Our server issues cookies to every visitor to the Apollo Duck websites. These cookies contain nothing more than a server generated number which is used to distinguish visitors from each other and ensure that your visit is private and separate from all other visitors to the site. These cookies help us to ensure your privacy. No personally identifiable information is recorded by the cookies. 

Copyright © 1998-2011 Santa Monica Airlines Ltd. 

| 

'Bauhaus' Eco-frie  
  
GBP 119,000.00

Boston Whaler  
  
GBP 11,500.00

60Ft 2007 Aqualine  
  
GBP 111,000.00

60Ft Aqualine Semi  
  
GBP 79,000.00

Freehold mooring +  
  
GBP 185,000.00

58' Semi Trad on R  
  
GBP 69,950

**Apollo Duck  
boats for sale  
worldwide:**

**UK**  

[Silicon Ink  
Property For Sale](http://www.siliconink.com/)
